pinnbank.com 2007-07-12

# Welcome To Pinnacle Bank Your Home For Online Banking

**»**   Personal BankingItems of InterestPrivacy Policy

 **Pinnacle Bank Customer Privacy Policy**

Our mission is to help customers meet their financial goals. Our objective is to provide customers with all the products and services they need to meet their financial goals.

We are committed to providing you the very best service, highest quality products, and valuable information about new services and benefits.

The Privacy Policy described in this disclosure may be amended at any time. We will keep you informed of any applicable changes at least annually or as required by law. The policy described here replaces all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter.

**Our Privacy Policy**  
We believe your privacy is of utmost importance, and Pinnacle Bank values your relationship and your trust. Keeping your nonpublic personal information confidential and secure is an important part of our responsibility to you. We take this responsibility very seriously.

**Confidentiality and Security**  
Pinnacle Bank restricts access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

Information Collection and Use  
By collecting and maintaining accurate customer information, we learn more about your needs and are better able to provide superior customer service to you.

We collect nonpublic personal information in order to:

  * Protect your accounts from unauthorized access or identity theft;
  * Provide superior service;
  * Provide you with products and services designed to meet your financial goals; and
  * Introduce you to special offers and opportunities available through our affiliates and others.

We collect and maintain nonpublic personal information from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications and other forms;
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and
  * Information we receive from a third party, such as a consumer reporting agency.

"Nonpublic personal information" is data about you that we may obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. This could include information such as account number(s), social security number, income, net worth, account balance(s), payment history, or overdraft history.

**Information Sharing  
**Because we value your relationship and hold your privacy with the utmost respect, we will not disclose your nonpublic personal information to anyone except those companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements, or as permitted by the law.

If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will adhere to the privacy policy described in this publication.

* * *

 Equal Housing Lender • Member FDIC
